Diana Davies Papers, 1960s-1996 (ongoing)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Women's Movement - Women's Lives
  - Women's movement miscellaneous
    - Theatre groups: "How to make a Woman Theatre"; members of NY Now and Radicalesbians; Leah Fritz book signing (includes Kady, Leah Fritz, Andrea Dworkin, Jill Johnson, Karla Jay, Marquita Rivera, others); class at Hunter College, 1972), 1969-75 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Conferences and women's play produced by "It's All Right to be a Woman Theatre" company. "Conference of the Beguines" (1975) includes filmmakers Carol Clement and Ariel Dougherty; musician Jeriann "Jeritree" Hilderely, Kady, others. Conference - Queens College (NY) - speakers includes Jill Johnson. Performance of "Lavender Jane" music group with Kay Gardner, Alex Dobkin, Patches Atom, New Paltz, NY, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Phyllis Birkby, activist, architect and others (includes June Arnold of Daughters pub.), Plainfield, VT, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Women's march press conference and women's march, NY (includes Jill Johnson, Martha Shelley, NY Radical Feminists, Motorcycle Women, "Lesbian - Feminist Take Over"), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Women picket the Playboy Club (NYC), 1970 (Box 7)
    - Women's Rights march and in support of Kate Millett; press conference for event and meeting to draft petition (includes K. Millett, Ivy Bottini, Flo Kennedy, Betty Friedan, March Hoffman, Ti-Grace Atkinson, Gloria Steinem, Barnard Women's Lib., Columbia U. Women's Liberation, etc.), circa 1970 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Women's strike march, Fifth Ave., NYC (Thousands, and patriarchal hecklers), 26 Aug, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Women's strike march, Rochester, NY, and march to home of Susan B. Anthony, 26 Aug., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Women's social and economic justice march and rally. Garment district, NYC (includes Kady, Susanna Shepard Shannon) Labor groups, Lesbians Unite! group, NY Radical Feminists, and angry cop and onlookers, Fall 1972 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Guerrilla Girls posters, NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Anti-porn street theatre, local women's feminist capers, Western Mass - Amherst (includes Kady), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Mary Daly reading at Amherst College (includes Sheila Pepe, Laura Pattison, Nancy Kelly, Pat Styer), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Drawings/poster and postcards feminist art - portraits by Diana Davies (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Portraits - photos - miscellaneous of feminist activists (includes Tower press - women's print shop. Z. Budapest) (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Portraits - miscellaneous feminist activists (includes Marchoff, "Sahm and Ann - mini feminist," Jess Klatzker) collages of photos (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Portraits - Harriet Desmoines, Ellen Berger, and Catherine Nicholson, co- founders - Sinister Wisdom journal. Western Mass, 1985 and 1991 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - NY Now and Radical Lesbian members (includes Donna Gottschalk, K. Millett, Jan Barber ,Ellen Shumsky, Arlene Kisner, others), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Bella Abzug, NYC, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Jill Johnson, NYC; portrait and feminist activist Arlene Kisner; portrait and Gay soup kitchen and poster, circa 1969 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Rita Mae Brown reading, NYC, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Ti-Grace Atkinson, 1976. Woodstock Women's Center, NY State (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Fighting violence against women
    - "An Appeal to our Neighborhood" sign in window denouncing woman's murder. Lower East side, NY, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - "Stop Snuff Movies" protests, NY city and state (includes Kady, Barbara Deming, others), 1974 and 1976 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Conference to stop sexual slavery. UMass Amherst (includes Alerte Balance and Ninotchka Rosca - Feminist-human rights activists), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 51-53)
    - Clothesline project - t-shirts in support of women who are victims of battering and murder. Smith College, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - "Witness to Violence" public art work against violence against women, Artspace, Greenfield, MA, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Violence against women - ads, signs, graffiti. Boston and NY, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Times Square porn theatre marquee and man with sandwich board "Jesus Saves," NYC, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous published work - tear sheets of feminist material (DJD) (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Un-published work, "Womanbeing" - a book that never was by DJD, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Photojourney
  - Introduction
    - "How to Use This Material" and copy of book, Photojourney by Diana Davies 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Reviews of Photojourney (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Extra Loose (unbound) pages of Photojourney: 150-line screen - suitable for reproduction, all media - print right from pages (acid free) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Info on miscellaneous color conversion and copy negatives for photos in book (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous b&w copy slides of photos of women in the book (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Photos
    - Book cover - Bessie who lives in Central Park, NYC, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Woman with umbrella (NY), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - "Just Call me Robin Hood" - "The Street Jester," circa 1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Gypsy children - Romany kids (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Shopping bag woman- "Irish Lace," 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - "Street Man - Street Flower" The Bowery, NY, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Woman crying, sitting on a carton (a "working girl" - prostitute) NYC, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Street singer (old man with accordion) Philadelphia, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Children of Paradise - kids in slum playground, NYC, early 1970s (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Homeless woman on mattress, NYC, 1980s (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Homeless man in his living room, late 1980s, NYC (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Two old women (legs of) with old cat. Lower East Side, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - "Street Opera Singer" (Box 9)
    - Street scenes: "Kill Hippies" graffiti, Bodega (grocery) Store, and storefront and kid "Marta" (Box 9)
    - "The Bowery Boys" homeless men and Catholic worker, NY, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Mary Lou Williams, Jazz musician, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Charles Azanavour, musician, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Bessie Jones, folklorist, folksinger; Georgia Sea Islands, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Gertrude Gough, seamstress, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Muhammad Ali, boxer, African-American rights activist, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Alexander Calder, sculptor, artist; and Benjamin Spock, doctor and peace activist, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Mississippi John Hurt, folksinger; Barbara Dane, folksinger, folklorist; Mike Bloomfield, guitarist, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Francine Winham, photographer and filmmaker, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Lotte Jacobi, photographer (and info), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - "The Hippies" (woman dancing) NY at a "Be-In," 1960s (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Monkey (animal), Washington Square Park, NY, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Jane Gapen, artist-writer and chicken, NY State, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - David Amram, jazzman, composer; and Ray Barreto, drummer, Latino music, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Kay Gardner, musician, composer, conductor, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Golda Meir, Israel, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Old man (Chinese), Chinatown, NY, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Victoria Spivey, blues musician, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Willie Mae "Big Mama" Thornton, blues musician, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Consuelo "Connie" Kanaga, photographer, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Ethel Merman, singer, performer in "Hello Dolly," Broadway, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Leontyne Price, opera singer at the "Old Met" Opera, NY, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Odetta, the folksinger, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - B.B. King, blues musician, Newport Folk Festival, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Henry Crow Dog - Lakota ("Sioux") medicine man- speaking tour on Native American culture, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - (Old woman) at the bus stop. Tel Aviv, Israel, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - May Sarton, poet/writer (and info), 1980s (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Alberta Hunter, jazz-blues singer, NYC café performer, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - "Gertrude," best friend (dog) 1971 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Children playing in Lower East side fire hydrants, NYC (Box 9)
    - Eileen Pagan, writer, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Sheila Pepe, artist. Ashfield, MA, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Dorothy Donegan, musician, jazz woman. Newton, MA, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - "Aunt Alice" the storyteller and herbalist. Viola, TN, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - "Friends, Lower East side, 1960s" (includes "Anna", who works in the Laundromat). They are doing tenants rights work (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Neo-Nazi's (US) and Right wing creeps with "Kill a commie for Christ" sign at pro-war demo, NYC, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Nighttime peace march, the old woman with Vietnam war victims' sign, and "Dump Nixon Demo," NYC, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Pro-war demo, Union Square, NYC, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Gen. William Westmoreland, "The Commander of US Troops in Vietnam," April 1967; and a protest of his speaking tour, NYC, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - "The Grenade Lesson"-- Soldier and instruction poser, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Draft card burning, Central Park NY. Massive protest of draft and war in Vietnam, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hand, with draft card burning. Sit-in protest by thousands at the Pentagon, Washington D.C., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Veterans for Peace (US capital building) Washington D.C., Vietnam veterans against the war (VVAW), thousands participated, 1971. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - "We Want Peace Now", boys with sign, NYC. Part of nation-wide moratorium against Vietnam War, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - War-wounded children in Biafra (W. Africa), circa 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Barbara Demig, writer, activist at Women's conference, NY State, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Campesinas, United Farm Workers (UFW), on tour to gain support for union, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - A.J. Muste, pacifist organizer, NYC, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Dom Helder [Pessoa Camra], called "Dom Helder" Brazilian human rights activist, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Rigoberta Menchu, human rights activist, speaking in Springfield, MA, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Agnes "Sis" Cunningham, folksinger, co-founder Broadside magazine. People's music activist, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Margaret Hold, "US Out of Central America" demo, Western Mass, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Kady, craftswoman, writer, at Michigan Women's Music Festival, with her traveling show of feminist silver crafts, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Joan Baez, folksinger, songwriter, pacifist activist, PA, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Freedom Now" Harlem supports the Sema (Alabama) Civil Rights Movement. Massive demo, NY, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - "Oh, Wallace, you never can jail us all" racist supporters of Alabama, Gov. George Wallace, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Ella Baker, civil rights and human rights activist, at a peace march, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Rosa Parks, civil rights activist, Atlanta, GA, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Civil rights worker, man with "SNCC" button on hat, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - One day after the murder of Martin Luther King Jr., NY (woman weeping, memorial rally), 1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Fannie Lou Hamer, civil rights organizer, co-founder Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party, 1965 and 1966 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Bernice Johnson Reagon, civil rights organizer, song leader, historian African American culture, founder "Sweet Honey in the Rock" song group, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - "I have a dream" civil rights rally and support for striking African-American sanitation workers. Memphis, TN, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - "Do not cross…" Harlem supports the Alabama Civil Rights Movement. (Woman with flag), NY, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Dorothy Day, poor people's rights activist, pacifist activist, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Malvina Reynolds, songwriter, folksinger, people's songs activist, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - [Woman] singer at a rally for poor people, Washington D.C., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - James Bevel, civil rights organizer, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Two women (profiles) on the poor people's march in U.S. South Caravan, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Buffy Sainte-Marie, folksinger -also- Jean Richie and Mable Hillery, folksingers, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Arlo Guthrie, folksinger (1966 or 1967) (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Andrea Dworkin, Woodstock (NY) Women's Center (1974 or 1976) (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Kate Millett, NY State (at her farm), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Teresa Trull (and dog), musician, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Sonia Johnson, on her Presidential campaign tour. Cambridge, MA, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - "Dismember Patriarchy" Kady with sign at "Stop Snuff Movies" demo. NYC and woman with "--End the war against women" sign and cops, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - New England Women's Symphony (news) rehearsal, Sanders Theatre, Harvard U., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Prisoners' rights demo at NYC women's house of detention, "House of D."; Women with signs "our sisters will be treated like human beings," 1970 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Woman with "Women" sign (surrounded by women's profiles) NYC demonstration (includes Kate Millett and Betty Friedan and demonstrators in support of K. Millett), 1970s (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - "Sisterhood is powerful", women's strike march. Rochester, NY. Women demonstrators go by sneering men, 26 Aug., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Women and children refugees at a refugee center in Biafra (W. Africa) during the war, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Three lifelong friends. 3-old women with stories and hats. In a parish hall (Gertie, Sadie, Mary), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Catfriends (cats on table) Catskill Mtns., NY State, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Refugee settlements (with donkey in street), Jericho, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Weeping woman, São Tomé Island, off the coast of Africa, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Seagull and seagulls and tugboats, Coastal Maine, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Friends, Lower East side, NY--graffiti reads, "Eddie" - boys in window, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Friends at market, "The Basket Shop" public market, Libson, Portugal, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Friends on porch (2 girls and 2 older women, mostly African-American neighborhood) Memphis, TN, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Healer of broken dolls (Esperanza) Havana, Cuba and her shop and friends and cat, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Child with clay vessel, Israel, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Country fair, Maryland (with "4-H" sign and beef cattle), 1970s (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Two women with pottery water vases. East Jerusalem, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Two women (generations), Washington D.C.; also - dumb racist cop with name tag removed from uniform; also - civil rights rally, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Janis Joplin (back cover of book), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Poverty - Poor Folk
  - Graffiti and Signs
    - "Gentrification is war" Northampton, Mass., late 80s early 90s (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Tenants' Rights Banner and "Sienbren Flores" graffiti. Lower East side, NY, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - "Please keep off the flowers" sign and community gardens, 1970, NYC (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - "There are a lot of hate on you" graffiti and squatters' rights sign, miscellaneous graffiti wall, 1972. and old woman in window, 2nd Ave., Lower East side (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - "Soul" graffiti wall. "Stinks" written on public school wall, 1971 and bocce players, Lower East side (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "Bomb the Suburbs" graffiti, Lower East side, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Community Organizing and Actions
    - Community organizers, 1968: Peggy Terry (ex-Appalachia) from Chicago. Myles Horton, Highlander Folk School, TN. Haskell Wexler filmmaker (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - "Mary" on the poor people's march, 1968. "Doc" (with beard) poor folk getting tear-gassed by D.C. cops tyring to drive them out of tent city, Washington D.C. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Sit-in at the dept. of agriculture, for food stamps and good food for poor people, 1968, Washington D.C. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Workers on the poor peoples campaign board bus for east Coast Caravan, 1968, NYC (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - "Love not hate" and girls with sign on poor people's march, NJ, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - "Mother poor, father too. But sister is going to change and so are you" woman with sign, 1968, Baltimore, MD (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - "I care" - woman with sign march against poverty, NJ, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Living wage campaign, 1996, Western Mass., "Anarchist community' banner carried by community organizers (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Tenants' Rights, Housing, Rent Strikes
    - Miscellaneous housing, homeless tenants' rights, 1960s on (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Tenants' rights organization: Kady and rent strike, 1970. 88 East 3rd St, NYC - huge banner, Lower East side (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - "Huelga de Renta" Kady and rent strike banner - making, 1971. Tenant community organizers, Lower East side, NY (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - "Rent strike against the city for decent housing" 1971. Kady and community organizers and tenants of city-owned buildings, Lower East side and info - poster (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Kady and Frances Goldin work with tenants on strike. Street meeting 1971, Lower East side (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Tenants' rights demo, 1970s. Kady and Larry Davis, organizers picket line, NY (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Esther Rand, East side tenants' council organizer and Larry Daivs, strike organizer, 1971. Kady and tenants' rights workers and info. Lower East side (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - City signs: "Go hang out someplace else" and "No Dumping" Brooklyn, NY, 1976. Vacant lots (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - "The Automat" - where poor folk hang out, sometimes all night, 1976 (there were several in NYC, now, no more) (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Joanie Ross, organizer and helper of poor women. 15th St. Quaker meeting, 1977. NYC (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Shelters, Soup Kitchens, Food and Clothing Services
    - "No more hunger" sign and people on poor people's campaign, 1968. Washington D.C. and older woman and little girl, at rally (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - "Bread - Free Forever" - community bakers, baked hundreds of loaves each day and gave these away, Washington D.C., 1968, poor peoples campaign and "Hunger's Wall" graffiti from the community ("Sissisters of Watts for Human Dignity" is written on wall) and bread recipe from bakers (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Catholic Worker Movement, "House of Hospitality" 1965 and homeless men. The Bowery, NYC (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Soup kitchens, food pantries, survival centers, clothing services, miscellaneous varied dates. Dumpster diving, streets survival (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Food Not Bombs
      - Western Mass and Philadelphia, late 1990s, free community food distribution and meals (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Food sharing, Pulaski Park, Northampton, Mass., 1990s (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Info, flyers, menus, etc. Western Mass and US info (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Soup kitchens and food pantries, Coastal Maine, 1993. Chris Greene, community organizer for poor people (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Yorkville Common: Pantry, NYC, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Info on community services for poor folk (miscellaneous) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Homeless People/Street People
    - Poor people, NYC. Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Bessie-who-lives-in-Central Park, NYC, 1970. Homeless woman and her lean-to in the park (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Poverty and poor folk, homeless people, slums, 1960s on, color slides (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Homeless men, fire in trash can for warmth. Graffiti on wal, NYC, 1965. Color slide and print (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Homeless, in NYC. Miscellaneous, 1960s and 1980s and early 1990s. People living on the street, bus station, in doorways (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Homeless man passed out in street, kids playing in vacant lot, vacant building and eviction "No Loitering" sign, murals. NYC, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Homeless person in doorway, Harvard Square, Cambridge, MA. Evicted people's belongings, Portland, ME. Graffiti and stickers Central Square, Cambridge, Mass., 1993 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Homeless man eating sandwich near curbside next to police cars. African- American celebration flags carried downtown, Philadelphia, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Homeless people, 1970 sleeping in doorways, various locations, NYC (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Graffiti - "Homeless R. Human 2" on railroad trestle, Northampton, MA. April 2001 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Kentucky Mtn. woman living in Washington D.C., 1968 -n 33 years old, 3 kids, husband an injured minor on poor people's march and poster design by DJD (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Poster designs by Diana Davies. Poor folks to pics (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Smokey Joe. A hobo and his dog, on the road in W. Virginia 1972 and clothing donation for the poor W. Virginia (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Old street men: "John", with Pete Kozlowski, Main St. Northampton, MA, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Homeless woman and child get temporary shelter in a rent-strike apt. in NY, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Man with backpack next to stretch limo, NY, 1980s (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Poor Kids
      - Poor kids' playgrounds (the uses of rubble) and children playing in street, on rooftops, in vacant lots, girl playing with wheels, on stairs of building. Lower East side, 1960s-70s (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - "Love is all we need", graffiti in vacant lot. Kids playing in lot, street scenes "Young Lords' Party" and Pureto Rican Liberation signs, old man in graveyard. Lower East side, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - "The Playground", East 3rd Str. vacant lot. Kids playing in lot and boy dragging tricycle (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Puerto Rican child in street, "Chelsea" section, NYC. Old woman sitting outside building delivery man with parcels on street, NYC, 1963 or 1964 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - The paper bag seller, Harlem, NY, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Graffiti, clothes dummy on street, man being arrested: Lower East side, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Immigrants
      - "The new Immigrants" - central American family in tenement, 1972, Lower East side, NY and Kady and Evan who are organizing this building's tenants (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Poor farmers/sharecroppers and their wagon. Viola, TN, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous writings and some published material on poor folk and drawings (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous poor folk photos, U.S., and some info (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Northampton State Hospital Squat and Squatters Housing Rights Material
  - The "Squat Book": photos and info. Contents of a touring scrapbook which traveled about with talks and exhibits on poor people and housing rights - "Book Project" (some of the photos are from the next bunch of folders) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Northampton State Hospital squat, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2-5)
  - Inside the buildings (interior) Northampton State Hospital (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Squat support rally, Pulaski Park and in front of Memorial hall and next to Unitarian Church, theatre, speakers, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "House the Homeless" banner-making by Kady, Linda Vannoni and Frances Crowe and demo for housing rights and to support the people who worked in the squats. Northampton, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)